export let questions = [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is the correct way to start a PHP script tag?",
      "description": "PHP script tag",
      "answers": ["<?php", "<script language='php'>", "<%", "<$php>"],
      "c_answer": "<?php"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid PHP variable name?",
      "description": "Invalid PHP variable name",
      "answers": ["$my-variable", "$myVariable", "$_myVariable", "$my_variable"],
      "c_answer": "$my-variable"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How do you concatenate two strings in PHP?",
      "description": "String concatenation in PHP",
      "answers": ["$str1 . $str2", "$str1 + $str2", "$str1 : $str2", "concat($str1, $str2)"],
      "c_answer": "$str1 . $str2"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which function is used to check if a variable is an array in PHP?",
      "description": "Check if a variable is an array",
      "answers": [ "array()", "check_array()", "validate_array()", "is_array()"],
      "c_answer": "is_array()"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What does the function `echo` do in PHP?",
      "description": "Purpose of the `echo` function",
      "answers": ["Calculates a mathematical expression","Outputs one or more strings", "Accepts user input", "Defines a function"],
      "c_answer": "Outputs one or more strings"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which of the following is used to end a PHP statement?",
      "description": "End of PHP statement",
      "answers": [";", ":", ".", ",",],
      "c_answer": ";"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What is the default method for submitting HTML forms?",
      "description": "Default form submission method",
      "answers": [ "POST","PUT",  "GET","DELETE"],
      "c_answer": "GET"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which PHP function is used to establish a database connection?",
      "description": "Establishing database connection",
      "answers": [ "db_connect()", "mysqli_connect()","connect_db()", "open_db_connection()"],
      "c_answer": "mysqli_connect()"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What does the `include` statement do in PHP?",
      "description": "Purpose of the `include` statement",
      "answers": ["Inserts the content of a file", "Deletes a file", "Renames a file", "Copies a file"],
      "c_answer": "Inserts the content of a file"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which PHP function is used to redirect the user to a different page?",
      "description": "Redirecting in PHP",
      "answers": [ "redirect()","header()", "location()", "forward()"],
      "c_answer": "header()" 
    }
  ]
  
